<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cryptocurrency on Hudson Jameson’s Website and Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/cryptocurrency/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cryptocurrency on Hudson Jameson’s Website and Blog</description>
    <image>
      <title>Hudson Jameson’s Website and Blog</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/images/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/images/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Hudson Jameson</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/cryptocurrency/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is an Ethereum core developer?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020-06-22-what-is-an-ethereum-core-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020-06-22-what-is-an-ethereum-core-developer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There has been a lot of debate around what makes someone an Ethereum core developer or what the term even means. I&amp;rsquo;m intimately involved in day-to-day operations involving Ethereum 1.0 protocol development as a developer liaison for the community and have been operating the Ethereum Core Developer call (a.k.a AllCoreDevs call) every other Friday since late 2016. The following is not definitive and only represents my opinion. Nothing in this blog represents the opinion of any of my employers or the Ethereum Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eth 2.0 Staking and More with Topaz and DAppnode for under $750</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020-05-18-eth-2-0-staking-and-more-with-topaz-and-dappnode-for-under-750/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020-05-18-eth-2-0-staking-and-more-with-topaz-and-dappnode-for-under-750/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ethereum 2.0 is the upcoming overhaul to the Ethereum blockchain protocol that will bring with it proof-of-stake (to provide more security) and sharding (to provide more scaling). It is being released in &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.ethhub.io/ethereum-roadmap/ethereum-2.0/eth-2.0-phases/&#34;&gt;at least 3 &amp;ldquo;phases&amp;rdquo;, labeled Phase 0 through Phase 2&lt;/a&gt;. It is anticipated that during Q3-Q4 of 2020 it will be launching Phase 0 of the upgrade that will deploy the &amp;ldquo;beacon chain&amp;rdquo;. The beacon chain, among other things, is meant to act as a coordinator between the different actors participating to secure the Eth 2.0 network. I wanted to join an Eth 2.0 Phase 0 testnet to help and get experience running a node. This article is going to detail the hardware and software set-up I went through to become an Eth 2.0 validator on the Topaz testnet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Protocol Development Governance and Network Upgrade Coordination</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020-03-23-ethereum-protocol-development-governance-and-network-upgrade-coordination/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020-03-23-ethereum-protocol-development-governance-and-network-upgrade-coordination/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This post will discuss how protocol level development decisions are made as well as how Ethereum network upgrades (a.k.a hard forks) are organized. There is a rich history in how Ethereum&amp;rsquo;s decision making processes have developed over time. This article will focus on Eth 1.0 governance and not touch on Ethereum 2.0 governance. This article does not represent the viewpoint of the Ethereum Foundation or any other entity that I am associated with.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProgPoW: The Ethereum Community Speaks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020-03-02-progpow-the-ethereum-community-speaks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020-03-02-progpow-the-ethereum-community-speaks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Programmatic Proof-of-Work (ProgPoW) has been a topic of contention in the Ethereum community for a long time. This post explains the history of ProgPoW, the various arguments for and against it, and my personal opinion on the topic. I am speaking on behalf of myself, Hudson Jameson, and not on behalf of the Ethereum Foundation or any other entity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;history&#34;&gt;History&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://eips.ethereum.org/EIPS/eip-1057&#34;&gt;ProgPoW&lt;/a&gt; is &amp;ldquo;a new Proof-of-Work algorithm to replace Ethash that utilizes almost all parts of commodity GPUs&amp;rdquo;. ProgPoW aims to decrease the economic incentive to build an Application-Specific Integrated Circuit (ASIC); a highly specialized device designed for a specific purpose, in this case, mining Ethereum much more efficiently than traditional GPU mining. ProgPoW is not designed to completely prevent a ProgPoW ASIC from being created, but rather make it expensive to build and not worth it to produce. It was submitted as &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ethereum/EIPs/blob/master/EIPS/eip-1.md#core-eips&#34;&gt;a core EIP&lt;/a&gt; on May 2, 2018, by a semi-anonymous group calling itself &lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@ifdefelse&#34;&gt;IfDefElse&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hudson&#39;s Zcash Developer Fund Proposal Reviews</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2019-11-15-hudsons-zcash-developer-fund-proposal-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2019-11-15-hudsons-zcash-developer-fund-proposal-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I spent the last two days going over every dev fund proposal and writing my thoughts. I have turned this into a post on the Zcash forums. I&amp;rsquo;m proud to be a part of the Zcash Foundation Advisory Board and I take this decision very seriously. I hope the community comes together on this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://forum.zcashcommunity.com/t/dev-fund-review-of-all-proposals-hudsons-review/35429&#34;&gt;Zcash Forum Post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/hudsonjameson/status/1195392941193342976?s=20&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skip to the bottom for my pick&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-am-i&#34;&gt;Who am I?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is Hudson Jameson and I am a cryptocurrency enthusiast who is involved in both the Ethereum and, to a lesser extent, Zcash community. I work for the Ethereum Foundation in a role for devops and community management. I hold a number of roles in the wider Ethereum ecosystem including EIP (Ethereum Improvement Proposal) Editor, Reddit moderator, Ethereum Cat Herders group co-founder, and core developer liaison responsible for organizing the bi-weekly Ethereum core developer calls. I am on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.zfnd.org/governance/community-advisory-panel/&#34;&gt;Zcash Community Advisory Panel&lt;/a&gt; that will be &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.zfnd.org/blog/updated-community-sentiment-timeline/&#34;&gt;polled (for sentiment collection) by the Zcash Foundation regarding NU4 proposals (dev fund proposals)&lt;/a&gt;. I care about Zcash and it&amp;rsquo;s community. I consider Ethereum and Zcash besties &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
