<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ketamine on Hudson Jameson’s Website and Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/ketamine/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ketamine on Hudson Jameson’s Website and Blog</description>
    <image>
      <title>Hudson Jameson’s Website and Blog</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/images/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/images/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Hudson Jameson</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/ketamine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mental Health Update: October 2019</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2019-10-25-mental-health-update-october-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2019-10-25-mental-health-update-october-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mental health update: I am doing a lot better. I have adjusted my medications and went through an experimental bi-polar/depression treatment in July called intravenous ketamine treatment. Ketamine is an anesthetic drug that has been used for since the 1960s as a pain reliever and sedative. Only recently has it been explored as a treatment for drug resistant depression, bipolar, chronic pain, and other things. My experience with the drug was very positive. After my first infusion I noticed an immediate difference. My depression was significantly lower. One interesting side effect was that my anxiety increased as my depression decreased. It is almost like the depressive part of my mental health was masking the severe anxiety side of it. This effect mostly went away as I continued treatment. I had six ketamine infusions over the course of about 3 weeks, steadily increasing my dosage with each infusion. Professional anesthesiologists administered the drug and monitored me so I felt safe.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
